TAMUNOSAKI NDAH FRONT END DEVELOPER.

Front End Developer with two years of experience working with HTML/CSS, JQuery, React.js, Tailwind's CSS to deliver exceptional customer experiences, Adept at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions, and determining customer satisfaction.

EXPERIENCE

JuzWeb Designs. Olaogun Estate, Agbado, OG, Nigeria

Front End Web Developer September 2021 – Present.

- Working with clients to develop the overall look and design of a website
- Writing website code with programming languages such as HTML, C++ and Java
- Producing, maintaining and modifying websites and user interfaces
- Incorporating applications, graphics, audio and video clips into client websites
- Creating tools that enhance the user's website experience
- Ensuring websites are accessible across many platforms, including laptops and smartphones

Tee's Computer Institute, Maiduguri, Nigeria Computer Instructor.

February 2018 – July, 2019

- Designs and teaches various computer courses for senior adults.
- Creates course outlines and writes instruction and review handouts for each of the different course
- Prepares the room and the computers for use before each class; attends to the proper shutdown of computers after classes.

Topmost Computer Institute, Borno, Nigeria. Computer Operator and Graphic Designer. May 2015 – December 2017

- Provides data by operating a computer.
- Determines sequence of operations by studying production schedule.
- Performs defined tasks per documented instructions/processes.
- Prepares equipment for operations by accessing software in computer.

CONTACT

6, Tunde Oduwoga street, Olaogun, Agbado, Ogun State.

Nigeria.

Tel: +23470841058

Email: ndahtamunosaki@gmail.com

TOOLS AND SOFTWARE

- HTML
- CSS
- TAILWIND CSS
- JQUERY
- REACT.JS
- JAVASCRIPT
- MS WORD
- PHOTOSHOP

SKILLS

- Creativity. While you may not be doing the design heavy lifting as a web developer, you still play a huge role in the creation and deployment of a website. ...
- Communication Skills. As a Front-End Developer, you'll likely be working on a team. ...
- Teamwork. ...
- Growth Mindset. ...
- Problem-solving.
- Attention to detail.
- Strong communication skills.
- Excellent problem-solving skills.
- A logical approach to work.

EDUCATION

- University of Maiduguri, Borno, Nigeria Bachelor of Fisheries.
 - 2018.
- Lagos State school of Programming, Lagos, Nigeria

Certificate in Front End Development.

2023